Guide to the Skylander newsletters of 3605th A&E Ellington Air Force Base MS 1019
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Skylander newsletters of 3605th A&E Ellington Air Force Base
1999-2016
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Bell, Don
MS 1019
.5 Linear Feet
The Skylander Newsletter Collection consists of the Skylander Newsletters created by Editor Don Bell for the members of the Ellington Field Air Force Base's 3605th Armament and Electronics Maintenance Squadron. The collection is a complete run from 1999 to 2016.
Biographical / Historical
Donald A. Bell, who goes by Don, grew up in Delaware County, Ohio where he graduated high school in 1949. He joined the United States Air Force in January 1950 where he was transferred to Ellington Air Force Base in the spring. Don received promotions up to Staff Sergeant by January 1952. After receiving an honorable discharge in January 1954, he enrolled in Otterbein College where he received his BA with teaching credentials. He later went on to earn a master's degree in Broadcast Education from The Ohio State University. After receiving his bachelor's degree, Don began teaching English at the Whitehall Yearling High School in 1958 while also taking care of the audio visual department. In 1974, he formed a TV Production Course that he taught after school for 17 years. Several of Don's students went on to prominent positions such as: chief vice president of Radio One; member of the PBS Board of Directors; and owner of an internationally known PR company. After retiring from the school system in 1991, Don became the Museum Curator for the Historical Aircraft Squadron Museum in 2000.
Content Description
The Skylander Newsletter Collection consists of the Skylander Newsletters created by Editor Don Bell for the members of the Ellington Field Air Force Base's 3605th Armament and Electronics Maintenance Squadron and a biographical note. The collection is a complete run from 1999 to 2016. The newsletter contains updates on the squadron members and their lives, historical articles about events that occurred during the members' time at Ellington, general memories, pictures, reunion information, and obituaries.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donald A. Bell donated the newsletters in April of 2022.
Index Terms
Subjects
Military
Document Types
newsletters
Places
Texas--Ellington Air Force Base
- Series I: Newsletters
  - Editor information, 2022 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Skylander newsletters, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Skylander newsletters, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 18)